homes.org 2007-12-29

# homes.org Privacy Policy

**homes.org Privacy Policy**  
homes.org is the one-stop destination for Americans of all walks of life to make use of our convenient tools and free information provided to lower the cost of living, save time and improve the overall quality of life. Practical tools provided by homes.org include a utility switching concierge, bill lowering service and an unbiased comparison shopping engine. It is the most user-friendly online marketplace with an unlimited supply of free information and resources. It is the one destination with unlimited possibilities.

homes.org can be contacted at:

**Phone:** 1-800-967-4082 

Mon-Fri: 9am - 9pm EST

**Mail:**  
homes.org  
3303 W. Commercial Blvd.  
Fort Lauderdale, FL 33309

**Email:**  

By visiting, using and submitting information to www.homes.org, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. homes.org recognizes your right to know how your information is collected and shared, so homes.org created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to disclose our current policies regarding your privacy and the use of your personally identifiable information. In addition, we take further measures to prevent unauthorized interception of your personally identifiable information, as outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is for this website only and does not apply to the personal information provided to us for any other services our visitors choose to accept from related companies of homes.org or those companies not owned or controlled by homes.org.

**(1) Security**  
We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. However, in the unlikely event that an unauthorized third party compromises homes.org's security system, homes.org is not responsible for any occurrences or damages directly or indirectly caused by an unauthorized third party ability to view, use or disseminate your submissions or transmissions to www.homes.org, or your personally identifiable information.

**(2) Visitor Information**  
We collect only the domain name, but not the email address of non-subscribing visitors to our website; the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email; aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit; user- specific information on what pages consumers access or visit; all necessary information submitted by a customer during the ordering process; and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information, personal information and/or site registrations. If we use this information in a manner different from the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to use. Any email address information volunteered by visitors of any homes.org, Elephant Group, Inc., their partner web properties, or, obtained from affiliated sources for the purpose of receiving email communications from homes.org, are governed by the homes.org email privacy policy

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our website and to customize the content and/or layout of our pages for each individual visitor. In the event of a national emergency or other similarly urgent situation, homes.org reserves the right to fully cooperate with the requests of government authorities and agencies and disclose to those entities all website user information and databases collected, compiled and/or maintained by homes.org. We will also share information when necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

**(3) Cookies**  
Like many other Internet websites, homes.org utilizes "cookies" to automatically track and store anonymous preferential information about you as you use and navigate www.homes.org. Registered users of this site may utilize advanced tracking features using cookies to enable site-specific features required by our shopping cart technologies. "Cookies" are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored on your hard drive by your web browser. Cookies track your personal preferences and activities, but in no way contain or refer to any personally- identifiable information. Information collected from users by homes.org's cookies includes, but is not limited to: (i) type of web browser; (ii) IP addresses; (iii) type of computer used; and (iv) home server domain names.

homes.org's use of cookies allows homes.org to aggregate certain information about its users. The aggregated information helps homes.org to serve you better by compiling user preferences and statistical data to improve the offerings and features of www.homes.org. homes.org may use the aggregated information to - among other things: (i) develop products; (ii) improve content; (iii) track and report advertising click- throughs; and (iv) customize website layouts. homes.org may also share, loan, rent, or sell this aggregated information to its affiliates and third parties, but keep in mind that the aggregated information contains absolutely no personally identifiable information.

If you do not want www.homes.org's cookies to be inserted into your hard drive, you can disable your hard drive's ability to accept and receive cookies through your web browser. However, keep in mind that if you disable your hard drive's ability to accept and receive cookies, you may not be able to fully utilize all of the features of www.homes.org.

**(4) Clickstream Data**  
We collect click-stream data and HTTP protocol elements through access logs. This information is not personally identifiable and is used for website and system administration including: research and development, user analysis and business decision-making.

**(5) Links to Other Internet Websites on www.homes.org**  
www.homes.org may contain links to other Internet websites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to www.homes.org. homes.org makes no representations or warranties about, nor is it responsible for, the Privacy Practices of other Internet websites. When you enter a linked Internet website, homes.org encourages you to read the Privacy Policy of that linked website, as its Privacy Policy may differ substantially from that of this Privacy Policy.

**(6) Privacy Policy Updates**  
homes.org developed this Privacy Policy as a manifestation of our firm commitment to disclose our current privacy and confidentiality policies to you. However, the Internet is rapidly evolving. With this in mind, homes.org reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time in its sole discretion and without notice.

Any information we collect from you is subject only to our most current Privacy Policy. You are advised and encouraged to visit www.homes.org on a regular basis to review our most current Privacy Policy, and review any changes that may have been made. Unless you elect to opt-out of our Privacy Policy, you agree to be bound by our most current Privacy Policy, including any changes that have been made since you originally provided homes.org with information.

If at any time you wish to opt-out of this Privacy Policy, please contact homes.org either at the postal address listed at the beginning of this Privacy Policy, or via email at: [info@homes.org](mailto:info@homes.org)

**(7) Minors**  
Children under the age of 18 are not eligible to use our services or transmit any personal information to us. Minors may only use this service in conjunction with a parent or guardian.

**(8) Your Questions, Comments & Complaints**  
homes.org encourages you to provide us with feedback regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have questions, comments or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please email us at: [info@homes.org](mailto:info@homes.org)

**(9) Governing Law; Arbitration**  
This Privacy Policy is governed and construed in accordance with the internal laws of the state of Florida, without regard for principles or conflicts of laws. Any civil action, claim, dispute or proceeding arising out of, or relating to, this Privacy Policy shall be referred to final and binding arbitration, before a single arbitrator, under the commercial arbitration rules of the American Arbitration Association in Broward County, Florida. You and homes.org shall select the arbitrator, and if you and homes.org are unable to reach agreement on selection of the arbitrator within thirty (30) days after the notice of arbitration is served, then the American Arbitration Association shall select the arbitrator.

Judgment upon any award rendered by the arbitrator shall be final, binding and conclusive upon you and homes.org, and your and homes.org's respective administrators, executors, legal representatives, successors and assigns, and may be entered in any court of competent jurisdiction. Notwithstanding the previous sentence, in no event shall either you or homes.org be entitled to punitive, special, indirect, or consequential damages, and both you and homes.org hereby waive your rights to any punitive, special, indirect, or consequential damages, including, but not limited to, damages for any loss of profit, revenue or business.

**(10) Miscellaneous**  
If any portion of this Privacy Policy is deemed unlawful, void or unenforceable by any arbitrator, this Privacy Policy as a whole shall not be deemed unlawful, void or unenforceable, but only that portion of this Privacy Policy that is unlawful, void or unenforceable shall be stricken from this Privacy Policy. The headings contained in this Privacy Policy are for convenience or reference only, are not to be considered a part of this Privacy Policy, and shall not limit or otherwise affect in any way the meaning or interpretation of this Privacy Policy. All covenants, agreements, representations and warranties made in this Privacy Policy, as may be amended by homes.org from time to time, shall survive your opting out of this Privacy Policy and the termination of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy represents the entire understanding and agreement between you and homes.org regarding the subject matter of this Privacy Policy, and supersedes all other previous agreements, understandings and/or representations regarding the same.
